How to create a virtual model with a virtual model
AI pose generator
Use keywords or reference pictures to easily create a virtual model pose.
Click on the virtual model in the top menu.
AI model pose generator
You can enter keywords to create a reference picture or upload a reference picture directly.
First, select gender.
Click on the keyword suggestion.
Click on the keyword suggestion to help you choose the right keyword.
Click on Keep Keywords.
Even if you use the same keywords, the AI pose picture will be re-created every time.
Therefore, click on the Keep Keywords button to keep the existing results as much as possible while updating the keywords.
According to the addition or modification of keywords, the results may be different from the existing results.
Click on random keywords.
The system will provide random,
random keywords.
Enter words that describe accurate words and not long sentences to generate more effective results.
Then, enter keywords.
Click on the Create button to create a virtual model pose based on your image.
When there are more online users, the creation process may take some time.
Format features
Switch from the Keyword Select Card to the Picture Select Card.
The picture in the background is a reference picture to upload the image.
Click on the upload button to add an image which fits the following guidelines.
It is highly recommended to use full-body images from head to toe to ensure high-quality AI posture.
Click the Save button to save the posture as a PAUSE file.
Now you can apply it to the virtual model you choose.
After creating a posture, you can turn on the display virtual model joints to adjust the posture.
You can also use the shortcut keys.
That's all for this video. See you in the next video.